오, 로스!
Hey, Ross.
너 있어서 다행이다
지퍼좀 올려줄래?
I'm so glad someone's here.
Could you zip me up?
- 그래
- 고마워
- Sure.
- Thank you.
여기오는 동안
지퍼 올려주겠단 사람이
Can you believe no one
between my apartment and here..
아무도 없는거 있지?
offered to do that for me?
인정머리 없는 사람들!
People.
웬일로 차려입었어?
So why are you so dressed up?
마이크가 데리러 온댔어
Mike's picking me up for a date.
그래? 잘돼가?
진지하게 발전하는 거야?
How's that going?
Is it getting serious?
모르겠어
마이크가 좋긴 하지만
I don't know. I don't know.
I mean, I like him.
내 1등급 고기를 진열장에서
내려놔도 될진
But am I ready to take
my Grade A loins off the meat market?
잘 모르겠네
I'm not quite sure.
난 네 남자 대하는 태도가
정말 존경스러워
You know, I really admire
your whole dating attitude.
넌 참 건강해, 난 걱정만 하거든
너무 빠르거나
It's so healthy. I'm always like,
"Is this moving too fast?
느린거 아닌가?
계속 만나도 될까? 등등..
Is this moving too slow?
Where's this going?"
그래, 넌좀
드라마틱한 편이지
I know.
You are a bit of a drama queen.
넌 나보다 훨씬 나아
만나는 남자마다 재밌게 즐기고
You're so much better off. You just
go from guy to guy having fun..
깊이 발전하지 않는다고
걱정하지도 않잖아
and not worrying that it
never turns into anything serious.
다 그런건 아냐
I wouldn't say "never."
깊은 사이도 있었어
You know, there is that guy.
그사람 있잖아..
Okay, well, what about..?
분명히 누군가 있을거야
Okay, there's gotta be someone.
그런사람 없었어
그래서 존경스럽다는 거야!
- There isn't! That's what I'm saying.
- Oh, my God, you're right!
맙소사, 정말이네!
그래, 그래도 넌 또 이렇게
데이트 할 준비가 돼있잖아
I know. And yet, here you are,
all ready for the next date.
어쩜 지금까지 한번도
그런 생각해본적 없어
I can't believe I never
realized this before.
서른 넘도록 남자를 깊이
사귀어본적 없다니
I'm in my 30s, and I've never been
in a long-term relationship.
나 뭐가 잘못된 거지?
Oh, my God, what's wrong with me?
아냐, 넌 잘못된거 없어
There's nothing wrong with you.
난 네가 결혼에 별로 관심
없는것 같다고 느낀것 뿐이야
I mean, you don't strike me as the type
of person that wants to get married.
나도 결혼하고 싶어!
I want to get married!
제발 울지마
No, please..
Please don't cry because of me.
내가 뭘 알겠니?
세번이나 이혼했는데!
I don't know what I'm talking about,
okay? I've been divorced three times.
넌 그래도 결혼은 해봤잖아
At least you've been married.
맙소사, 네가 부러워지다니
말도 안돼!
Oh, my God!
I want to trade lives with Ross?!
피비?
Phoebe.
- 무슨 일이에요?
- 우리 데이트가 너무 기대돼서요
- What's wrong?
- Nothing. I'm excited about our date.
마이크, 이쪽은 로스 겔러
로스, 이쪽은..
Mike, this is Ross Geller.
Ross, this is Mike..
- 잘못알아 듣겠네요
- 마이크 해니건이에요
- Sorry, I didn't catch that.
- Mike Hanigan.
로스 겔러입니다
- Ross Geller.
- Hey.
- 정말 가도 되겠어요?
- 네
So are you sure you're ready to go?
내 얼굴 어때?
How do I look?
- 가방속에 거울 있니?
- 아니
- Do you have a compact in your purse?
- No.
아주 보기좋아
You look great.
프렌즈 시즌 9
'환상 속의 상어'
- 안녕?
- 어서와, 저 여자
- Hey, Joey.
- This girl won't turn around.
뒷모습만으론 예쁜지 잘 모르겠어
어떤것 같아?
I can't tell if she's hot or not.
What do you think?
너랑 여자 놓고
품평회 할 생각 없어
Joey, I am not going
to objectify women with you.
하지만 저 여자 얼굴이
엉덩이만큼만 된다면..
But if her face is
as nice as her ass..
- 우와!
- 고마워
- Mama!
- All right. Thanks.
- 챈들러랑 통화했니?
- 이번 주말에는 털사에 있어야 한대
- Have you talked to Chandler?
- He has to stay in Tulsa this weekend.
- 왜?
- 몰라, 일이 많대
- How come?
- I don't know. He has to work.
뭔지 중요한 일이..
There's some big rush on the..
내 참! 요즘은 챈들러 일 얘기에
귀를 기울여야 한다니까
Damn it. I'm gonna have to start
listening when he talks about his job.
네가 그쪽으로 날아가서
놀라게 해주면 어때?
Why don't you fly out there
and surprise him?
그러고 싶지
그이가 너무 그리워
I'd love to. I really miss him.
근데, 그럴수 없어
하루밖에 안쉬고 표가 너무 비싸
But I can't. I have one day off
and it's just too expensive.
재밌군, 비행기표 값이
챈들러보다 더 중요하다?
Interesting. So Chandler's not worth
the price of a plane ticket to you.
그럴리 없지
Of course he is.
갈까?
Maybe I will go.
그래! 털사의 호텔에서
두번째 허니문을 보내는 거야
We'll have a little second honeymoon
at the Tulsa Ramada.
그거 꼭 가져가라, 가터가 붙어있는
비치는 검은색 속옷 말야
You should bring your black see-through
teddy with the attached garters.
나한테 그런 옷 있는거
어떻게 알았어?
- How do you know I have one of those?
- Didn't until just now.
그냥 찍은거야
얼굴이 대체 어떤거야?
Hot. Not hot.
앗싸!
Hot!
뭐라구요?
Excuse me?
당신이 멋지다고 했어요
I said that I think you're hot.
굉장히 쑥스럽네요
And.. now I'm embarrassed.
난 인사한줄 알았어요
I thought you said "hi."
그편이 훨씬 자연스러웠을 텐데
That would've been better.
안녕, 난 조이예요
I'll try that. Hi, I'm Joey.
헤일리예요
I'm Hayley.
보통은 카페에서 만난 분한테
데이트 신청하지 않는데..
Look, I don't normally ask out women
that I meet in coffeehouses.
감기 조심해요!
Gesundheit.
하지만..
But..
정말 쑥스럽네요
제가 좀 숫기가 없어서요
This is hard. I'm kind of shy.
기침 소리가 안좋은데
병원 한번 가보시죠
Seriously, you should see someone
about that cold.
더 심해지면 죽을수도 있다구요!
If it gets much worse, you could die.
우리 데이트해요
- Anyway..
- I would love to go out with you.
정말요? 잘됐네요
Really? Great.
내가 데이트 신청을 했던가요?
Did I..?
Did I actually ask you?
그러고 싶은것 같아서
내가 수고를 덜어 준 거예요
That's just where you were going.
I figured I'd help you out.
이런일 익숙하지
않은가 봐요?
You don't seem like the kind of guy
who does this a lot?
건터, 그 감기
빨리 병원에 가봐요!
Damn it, Gunther, you gave it to me.
어, 너구나
Oh, it's you.
콩으로 만든 핫도그도
갖고 왔지
With vegetarian corndogs.
그러지마
우리 얘기좀 하자
Come on, I just want to talk to you.
무슨 얘기?
내가 애 낳기는 글렀다고?
About what? How few ova I have left?
어제일 때문에 사과하려고
Come on, I just wanna apologize
for what happened yesterday.
미안해, 피비
I'm sorry, Phoebe.
괜찮아, 로스
That's okay, Ross.
- 그래, 데이트 어땠어?
- 끔찍했어
- So how'd the date go?
- Well, it was awful.
저녁도 겨우 먹었지
I barely got through dinner.
네 말 생각날 때마다
울음이 터졌거든
Every time I thought about
what you said, I cried.
아마 마이크도 내 괴상한
모습 때문에 밥도 못먹었을 거야
I'm pretty sure he spent most of the night
just staring at me in horror.
근데, 확실히는 모르지
내눈이 부어서 앞이 안보였거든
But I couldn't know for sure
because my eyes were swollen shut.
내가 널 울게 하려고
그런거 아니잖아
You know I wasn't trying
to make you cry.
난 네게 칭찬을 하려고 한거야
I was really trying to say something nice.
내가 하고 싶었던 말은
네가 진지한 관계를 갖진 못했지만..
I was basically saying even though
you've never been in a serious relationship..
- 또 시작이니?
- 미안
- Are we gonna do this again?
- Sorry.
- 마이크는 다시 전화 안했어?
- 너라면 이런 여자한테 걸겠니?
- So he hasn't called?
- Would you call this girl:
"오늘.. 저녁.. 즐거웠어요"
"Thanks for.. a lovely.. evening"?
정말 미안해
다 내 잘못이야
Now I feel terrible.
This is all my fault.
네가 정말 미안해야 할게
뭔지 알아?
You know what you should
feel terrible about?
내가 마이크와 진지한 관계가
될수도 있었다는 점이야
This could have been my serious guy.
친절하고 똑똑하고 재밌고
He was sweet and smart and funny.
그런 남자 만나기가
쉬운줄 알아?
You know how hard it is
to meet a guy like that?
나 같은 사람이 좀 드물지
We are a rare breed.
마이크일지도 몰라
Hey, maybe that's him.
여보세요?
Hello?
잠깐만 기다려줄래요?
Could you hold on one sec?
- 개인적인 전화야
- 마이크야?
- I need some privacy.
- Is it Mike?
아니, 장난 전화야
내가 남자 가리게 생겼냐?
No, it's a heavy breather.
I'll take what I can get.
듣고 있어요
I'm listening.
저녁 맛있었어요
What a great dinner.
케이크 마지막 조각 내게 준거
다시 한번 고마워요
Thanks again for letting me have that
last piece of cake at the restaurant.
천만에요
커피 만들께요
You're welcome again.
I'm gonna go make some coffee.
- 필요한거 없어요?
- 케이크 있어요?
- Can I get you anything?
- Do you have any cake?
잘되어 가는걸?
So this is going pretty good.
식사도 좋았고
공통점도 많단 말야
Dinner was nice.
We've got a lot in common.
와, 빅토리아 시크릿!
Victoria 's Secret.
독서 취향도 같네!
We even like the same books.
저 그림은 무시무시한데?
There's a scary painting.
잠깐만
Wait a minute.
전에도 이 그림보고
무서워했던것 같아
I think I've been scared
by that painting before.
이집도 낯이 익은걸
You know what?
This whole place looks familiar.
맞아! 여기 와본적 있어!
I have definitely been
in this apartment.
이 괴상한 나무도 본적있고
I know I've seen
this weird plant before.
지난번에도 찔렸는데
It did that the last time!
맙소사! 저 여자하고
전에 데이트한적 있어
Oh, my God.
I've gone out with this girl before.
맞아! 이 소파에서 잠도 잤고
Yeah! We had sex on this couch!
저 의자에서도..
아냐
And then on that chair, and..
No.
여기선 안했어
No, we didn't do it here..
이상하네, 딱 좋은 장소인데
which is weird, because it seems
like a perfectly good place.
아야! 이래서 안했구나
That's why.
마이크? 갑자기 찾아와서 미안해요
들어가도 될까요?
Hey, Mike. Sorry to just drop by
like this. Can I come in?
그럼요
Sure.
그런데 누구시죠?
Who are you?
로스예요
카페에서 만났던 피비 친구
I'm Ross. Phoebe's friend
from the coffeehouse?
마이크한테 할 중요한
얘기가 있어서 왔어요
I really, really need to talk
to you about something.
좋아요
설마
Unless..
무슨 종교 믿으라는건
아니겠죠?
You're not gonna try
and get me to join a cult, are you?
아녜요
그런 사람처럼 보여서요
No, it's just, you know,
you have that look.
망할놈의 미용실!
Damn Supercuts!
- 무슨 일이죠? 피비 괜찮아요?
- 네
- Well, what's up? Is Phoebe okay?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
피비는 괜찮아요
Phoebe is great. But..
제가 바보같은 짓을 했어요
I'm an idiot, okay?
아까 두사람 나가기 직전에
Right before you guys went out..
내가 피비 기분을 상하게 했어요
I accidentally got her all upset.
그래서 오늘 이상했군요
That's why she was weird.
그래요
Yes. Yeah, I..
피비 더러 남자를 깊이 사귀어
본적 없어 좋겠다고 했거든요
Yeah, I said something stupid about her
never having had a serious relationship.
하지만 피비는 아주 재밌고
멋진 여자니까
But you should know, she is
so much fun. A wonderful person.
- 포기하지 말아요
- 포기할 생각 없어요
- Please, don't blow her off.
- I'm not gonna blow her off.
방금 전화도 했는걸요
내일 저녁 만날 거예요
I just spoke to her.
We're going out tomorrow night.
우리 만나는거 괜찮죠?
카페에서 만난 낯선 손님
I mean, I hope that's okay with you,
stranger from the coffeehouse.
잘됐네요, 근데..
우는 모습이 싫지 않았어요?
That's great. So the crying
didn't turn you off?
난 조울증 있는 여자랑
9년 사귀다 헤어진 사람이에요
I just got out of a nine-year relationship
with a manic-depressive.
그 여자에 비하면
피비는 발랄한 거예요
Compared to that,
Phoebe's a Mousketeer.
제가 괜히 성가시게 했군요
Well, then, I didn't need
to bother you.
제가 괜한짓 한게
댁이 벌써 다섯 번째예요
You or the four other
Mike Hanigans I bothered.
그중 한명은 덩치도 크고
절 꼬시는것 같았어요
One of whom was quite large
and a little flirty.
잠깐만요
그말 사실이에요?
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Is that true what you said?
피비가 남자를 깊이
사귀어본적 없다는거?
Phoebe's never had
a serious relationship?
물론 있죠
Of course she has.
정말 깊이 사귄적이 없다면
If she's never had
a serious relationship..
내가 이렇게 떠들고 다니겠어요?
do you think I'd go
around broadcasting it..
구제불능 멍청이처럼?!
like some kind
of unstoppable moron?
- 그렇게 말했잖아요
- 네, 물론 그랬죠
- But you did say it.
- Yes. Yes, I did.
그런데 뒤에 말안한
And I will also say..
부분이 있어요
what I'm about to say..
뭐냐하면..
vis-a-vis..
끝까지 들어봐요
the following.
피비는 한번도 깊은
관계를 가진적이 없어요
Phoebe has never had
a serious relationship..
전에..
since..
한 남자와
아주 아주 진지하게 사귄
her super-serious relationship..
이후로요
with..
비크람이란 남자였죠
Vikram.
- 비크람?
- 진짜 이름 맞아요!
- Vikram?
- What? That's a real name.
오클라호마! 평야를 휩쓰는
저 바람은 어디서 오는가
제발 그만!
Stop it!
왜 날 텍사스로 보내주지
않은거지?
Why couldn't they have
sent me to Texas?
일곱시네
Seven o'clock.
운동하러 가야지
Maybe I'll hit the gym.
오, 농담하냐?
포르노나 보자!
Who am I kidding?
Pay-per-view porn.
- 들어오지 마세요!
- 놀랐지?
- Do not disturb! Do not disturb!
- Surprise!
- 모니카?
- 별일 없는거지?
- Monica?
- Is everything all right?
그럼, 다 좋아
난 그냥..
Yeah, everything's great.
I was just..
TV보고 있었어
watching some
regular television there.
멋진 깜짝 선물인걸!
What a pleasant surprise.
- 가서 좀 씻을게
- 그래
- I'm gonna go freshen up, okay?
- Okay, honey.
하마터면 들킬 뻔했다!
That was close.
오, 텍사스의 노랑장미
여긴 텍사스가 아냐
- 여보세요?
- 레이첼, 나야
- Hello.
- Hey, Rach, it's me.
방금 챈들러 만났는데
글쎄, 혼자..
Okay, I just got to Chandler's room,
and I caught him..
손장난하고 있더라구!
molesting himself.
못볼걸 봤구나
That couldn't have been pretty.
하지만 남자들은 다 그래
But you know, guys do that.
그래? 그런데 이상한건..
Well, the weird part is..
상어가 나오는 프로그램을
보면서 하더라구!
he was getting off..
to a shark-attack show!
- 설마!
- 정말이야!
- No!
- Yes! Chandler watches shark porn!
상어 포르노를 보고 있었어!
- 상어를 보면서?
- 그래
- While watching sharks?
- Yeah.
손장난하고 있던거 맞아?
Are you sure that's what
he was doing?
그렇게 펄쩍 뛰며 당황하는 꼴
한두번 본줄 아니?
You know how many times
I've seen him jump up like that?
뭐하고 있었는지는 뻔해
Believe me, I know what he was doing.
어쩜, 웬 상어?!
Man! Sharks!
챈들러한테 괴상한 구석이
있을줄 알았다니까
I always knew there was something
weird about that dude.
하지만 어떤 경우에도
사랑하겠노라 약속했잖아
You promised to love him
no matter what.
그야 병들거나, 살인을 하거나
했을 경우지
"What" means, like, if he
gets a disease or kills someone.
죠스보고 흥분하는 경우를
말한건 아니었어!
Not if he gets his jollies to Jaws.
하지만, 남자들은
우리랑 달라
You know what, honey?
Guys are just different.
도저히 이해 안되는걸
좋아하곤 한다구
They like things
that we can't understand.
한번은 사귀던 남자가
I once dated this guy
who wanted to pretend..
고고학자 흉내를 내고 싶어해서
that he was an archeologist,
and I was this..
난 그 남자가 얼음 속에서 녹여낸
선사시대 여자 역을 했다니까
naughty cavewoman
who he unfroze from a block of ice.
혹시 우리 오빠 얘기니?
Are you talking about my brother?
응, 아닌척 하려고
했는데 잘 안됐네
I didn't disguise that very well, did I?
- 안녕
- 어서와
- Hey.
- Hi.
어제 어떤 여자랑 데이트를 했거든
그런데 전에 사귄적이
I went out with this girl last night.
Halfway through our date I realized..
있는 여자야!
I already slept with her.
뉴욕 여자들 다 사귀어서
다시 한바퀴 도는거야?
You've slept with all the women in N.Y.,
and now you're going around again?
이상한건 그게 아냐
That's not even the weird part.
그 여자가 나랑 잤던걸
기억 못하더라구!
- She didn't remember sleeping with me!
- You don't remember sleeping with her.
너도 처음에 기억 못했잖아
그 여자는 기억해야지!
난 잊기 힘든 남자라구!
But she should remember sleeping
with me. I am very memorable!
- 너희들도 알잖아
- 어떻게 알아?
- You guys know.
- How do we know?
- 너랑 자본적이 없는데
- 그게 내 잘못이냐?
- We've never slept with you.
- And whose fault is that?
뭐 어때? 너도 기억 못하고
그 여자도 기억 못하잖아
What's the big deal?
You forgot, she forgot.
- 그날 컨디션이 나빴나보지
- 야!
- Maybe you were having an off night.
- Hey!
난 밤에 그런적 없어!
I never have an off night. Okay?
가끔 내가 좀 거만해지면
덜 섹시하긴 하지만
Although, sometimes if I'm
a little bloated, I don't feel that sexy.
그럴때도 항상 최고였다구!
But even then, I'm better than most!
그냥 잊어버리고
다시 데이트 신청해봐
Honey, why don't you just let it go
and ask her out again?
둘다 바람둥이라 누구랑 잤는지
기억 못하나보지
You're both so slutty, you don't
remember who you slept with.
천생연분이네
You're made for each other.
그거 말된다
Interesting.
한번 더 만나서 그냥
넘겨보도록 할께
Well, I'll go out with her again
and I'll try to get past it.
이번엔 폼잡지 말아야지!
No salt! Bloaty!
- 조이?
- 왜?
- Joey?
- What?
너 상어가 섹시하다고 생각해?
You don't think
sharks are sexy, do you?
아니
No.
잠깐, '인어공주'는
상어가 아닌가?
Wait a minute.
Wait, what was the Little Mermaid?
열렸어요
It's open!
어서와! 마이크가 전화했어
우리 다시 만날꺼야! 신난다!
- Hey.
- Mike called! We're going out again!
빨리 얘기하고 갈께
나 마이크 찾아갔었어
Quick thing.
I went to talk to Mike.
뭐?
What?
가서 뭐라고 했어?
What did you..?
What did you do, Ross?
들으면 너 화낼거야
Oh, boy. You got mad at that part.
내가 마이크한테 갔던건
I went over there, you know,
to tell him how..
네가 얼마나 괜찮은 여자인지
말하려고 간거야
How great you are. But..
그런데 나 알잖아
이러쿵저러쿵..
Well, you know me.
Blah-blah-blah.
- 어쩌다보니 결국 마이크한테..
- 뭐라고 했는데?
- And I ended up telling him that..
- What?
비크람이란 남자와 6년 간
You had a six-year-long relationship..
깊은 사이였다고 했어
with a guy named Vikram.
뭐? 왜?
What? Why?
네가..
Well, he seemed..
남자와 깊이 사귀어 본적
없다고 했더니 충격 받더라구
to bum hard when I told him you'd
never been in a serious relationship.
네가 내 친구가 낳은
아기의 아빠만 아니라면
If you hadn't just had a baby
with my best friend..
악마에게 맹세컨대..
I swear to Lucifer..
지금 당장 미친개가
네 물건 물어뜯게 했을거야!
a rabid dog would be feasting
on your danglers right now!
비크람에 대해 알게되면
I think you'll feel differently
when you know..
기분이 좀 나아질 거야
a little bit about Vikram.
비크람은
Okay, he's a..
연 디자이너야
He's a kite designer.
그리고 오프라 윈프리와
사귄적이 있어
And he used to date Oprah.
네가 지어낸 거짓말에
장단맞출 생각없어
I'm not going along
with some lie you made up, Ross.
- 마이크한테 사실대로 말할거야
- 좋아
- I'm just gonna be honest with him.
- Good.
그럼 사실대로 말해
Just be honest with him.
- 그래, 나 창피한거 없어
- 그럼
- I have nothing to be ashamed of.
- No.
좋아, 난 남자를 한달이상
사귀어 본적이 없어
So I haven't been in a relationship
that lasted longer than a month.
애인다운 애인을
가져본 적이 없다구
Okay? I haven't had a real boyfriend.
마이크가 그걸 감당 못하면
떠나는 거지, 뭐, 아마 떠날거야
If he can't handle it,
then he can leave. Which he will.
괜찮아, 난 죽을 때까지
혼자겠지!
And, you know, that's okay.
So I'll just be alone forever.
괜찮을 거야!
You know, all right.
It'll be fine. It'll be fine.
과부와 레즈비언들과
관광 다니면 되지
I'll go on walking tours
with widows and lesbians.
- 내가 열께
- 그래
- I'll get it.
- Okay.
내가 문만 열면
댁이 서있군요
I'm trying to remember the last time
I opened a door and you weren't there.
피비, 괜찮아요?
Phoebe, are you okay?
네..
마이크에게..
Yeah. There's just..
할말이 있어요
There's something you should know.
방금 비크람이 전화했어요
Vikram just called.
25년을 같이 살다가
이혼이라니 충격이었죠
So it was really a shock
after 25 years of marriage..
우리 부모님 같은 완벽한 커플이
이혼이라니, 난 막내였기 때문에
my parents getting divorced.
I took it the hardest..
- 제일 힘들었어요
- 네, 그랬군요
- because I was the youngest.
- Sure. Yeah.
어떻게 날 기억 못하죠?!
How can you not remember me?
네?
What?
어떻게 우리가 함께 잤던걸
기억 못 하냐고요!
How could you not remember
that we slept together?
- 뭐라고요? 언제요?
- 나도 몰라요!
- What? When?
- I don't know!
당신과 잤다면
기억 못할리가 없어요
I really, really think
I would remember sleeping with you.
한번 잘 생각해봐요
자..
Come on, come on.
Search your brain, all right? It was..
과거의 어느 날이에요
우리 둘다 여기 있었고
a certain amount of time ago.
I was here. You were here.
여기, 여기서 관계를 가졌죠
We had sex here, here, here..
저기에선 안했고요
Not there.
- 기억나요?
- 전혀 기억 안나요
- Anything?
- No, it's not ringing any bells.
어떻게 그럴수가 있어요!
My God, woman!
만나서 기억도 못하는 남자가
대체 몇이나 되는 거예요?
How many people have you been with
not to remember this?
나 왔어
저 문고리 빨리 고쳐야겠다
Hey, Hayley.
We really gotta fix that doorknob.
조이?
Joey?
당신이랑 잤군!
I slept with you!
그쪽은 나 확실히 기억하죠?
내 매력은 건재 하다니까!
And you obviously remember me!
Hey, I still got it!
만나서 반가웠어요
So we're good.
알아서 나갈게요
I'll let myself out.
비크람에게 외로울 때마다
And I said, "Okay, Vikram..
내게 전화할 권리 없다고 했죠
you can't just call
every time you get lonely.
레이첼과 사귈땐
그 권리 포기했지 않느냐고요
You gave up that right
when you slept with Rachel."
레이첼? 얼마전 로스의
아기를 낳았다는 친구?
Rachel? I thought she just
had a baby with Ross.
맞아요, 그게..
Yeah, well..
맞아요
Yeah.
엠마의 출생증명서에는
아버지가 로스라고 돼있지만
But Emma's birth certificate
might say "Geller"..
눈을 보면
비크람의 모습이 보이죠
but her eyes say "Mukherjee."
말도 안돼요, 무엇보다도 그 남자
본드 냄새 맡는다면서요?
That is so wrong.
And on top of that, he's a glue sniffer?
하지만 그이 전화를 받으면
마음이 움직여요
I know. But he calls,
and my heart goes to him.
그 프리랜서 연 디자이너가
말은 번드르르 하게 잘하거든요
You know, that bastard is one
smooth-talking freelance kite designer.
원한다면..
내가 손좀 봐줄수 있는데
If you want, I'll mess him up for you.
- 정말 그래 줄래요?
- 물론이죠
You would do that?
근데, 그남자 덩치가 커요?
덩치가 크다면..
Unless he's big.
If he's really big, I'll send him..
무례한 편지를 보낼께요
a rude letter.
당신과 어울리는
더 좋은 남자가 있을 거예요
I think there's somebody
better out there for you.
그게 나라는 얘기는 아니지만..
I mean, you know, I'm..
I'm not saying me, but..
나일수도 있잖아요?
Maybe.. me.
나에 대해 본드 냄새 같은건
걱정 안해도 될거예요
And you don't have to worry about
glue-sniffing with me.
가끔 매직펜 냄새를
맡긴 하지만요
Although, I do smell
the occasional Magic Marker.
어쨌든 나 피비를 행복하게
Yeah. Anyway, I just..
해줄수 있을것 같아요
I think I can make you happy.
- 도저히 못하겠네요
- 뭐 잘못됐어요?
- Okay, I can't do this.
- What's wrong?
비크람이란 사람은 없어요
로스가 지어낸 얘기예요
Well, there is no Vikram.
Ross made him up.
나 정말
Because I..
남자를 진지하게
사귀어 본적 없거든요
I really never have been
in a long-term relationship.
남자랑 함께 살아본 적도
기념일 챙겨본 적도 없어요
I've never lived with a guy. I've never
even celebrated an anniversary.
그래서..
So..
그런 내가 감당이
안된다면..
If that's too weird for you..
날 떠난대도 이해해요
and you want to leave,
I understand.
어색하지 않게
눈감고 있을게요
In fact, I'll close my eyes
to make it less awkward.
키스했네요?
You kissed me.
나 괴짜 같지 않아요?
- You don't think I'm a total freak?
- No.
글쎄..
Well..
약간..
Look, can I..?
괴짜 같긴 하지만
솔직한 성격이
Can I think you're a little weird
and also cool..
마음에 들고 키스하고 싶어요
for telling me the truth
and also want to kiss you?
좋아요
I guess so.
나한테 키스한거 멋져요
Can I think it's cool
that you kissed me..
한번 더 하고 싶나요?
and also want to kiss you again?
그리고 매직펜에 대해
좀 걱정해도 될까요?
And be a little concerned
about the Magic Markers?
물론이죠
Definitely.
나 비크람이야!
This is Vikram.
과거에 진지했던 우리의 관계에
대해 할 얘기가 있어
I need to talk to you about
the long-term relationship we had.
전화줘
연 제작 스튜디오에 있어
Call me. I am in my kite-making studio.
자기야, 나 왔어!
Hi, honey, I'm home.
안녕
Hi.
- 비행 어땠어?
- 좋았어
- How was your flight?
- It was great.
기내에서 물놀이 튜브를 주문했어
I ordered a pool float from the Sky Mall.
왜 그랬을까?
Why'd I do that?
편안하게 앉아
Why don't you sit down.
편안하게
Get yourself comfortable.
자기 놀라게 해줄
Because I have a little..
깜짝 선물이 있어
surprise for you.
지금 털사는 다섯 시겠군
Well, well, well.
It must be 5:00 in Tulsa..
뉴욕은 '섹스타임'이니까!
because it's "sex o'clock" in N.Y.C.!
이걸 보면 내가 얼마나
자길 사랑하는지 알거야
Okay.
This is how much I love you.
거대한 백상어는..
The great white..
모니카?
Honey?
내가 왜 상어 떼가 몰려다니는
비디오를 보고있지?
Why am I watching
a bunch of sharks swimming around?
왜? 저 장면은 싫어?
Is this..?
Is this not the good part?
앞으로 돌려서 상어이빨
나오는 장면 틀까?
Do you want me to fast-forward
to something.. toothier?
비디오를 제대로 고른건지
궁금해서 그래
No, I'm just not sure that you
got the right movie, that's all.
그 비디오 가게에 있는
상어비디오는 저것 뿐이야
This is the only one
they had at our video store.
악어킬러라는건 있던데
Though they did have something
called Crocodile Killers.
꼭 상어여야 해?
Or does it always have to be sharks?
뭐가 꼭 상어여야 해?
Does what always have to be sharks?
우리 다른 것도 해보자
Look, we can do something else.
내가 욕조에 들어가서
막 몸부림치는건 어때?
Do you want me to
get into the tub and.. thrash?
- 대체 왜그래?
- 괜찮아
- What's going on?
- It's okay. It's okay.
그래도 난 자기 사랑해
I still love you.
- 나도 같이 껴줘
- 나야말로 좀 껴주라!
- Let me be a part of this.
- Let me be a part of this!
털사에서 자기 하는거 봤어
I saw what you were doing in Tulsa.
자기 성난 상어떼 보면서
흥분했잖아!
Angry sharks turn you on!
그런적 없어
No, they don't.
그럼 왜 상어 보면서
혼자 즐겼어?
Then why were you watching them
and giving yourself a treat?
맙소사!
자기 들어와서 채널 바꿨어!
Oh, my God! When you came in,
I switched the channel.
보통 포르노 보고 있었다고!
I was just watching regular porn.
정말?
Really?
그래! 뻔한 미국식
'여자 대 여자' 포르노였어!
Yes. Just some good, old-fashioned,
American, girl-on-girl action.
지금 내가 얼마나
기쁜지 알아?
Can I tell you how happy
that makes me?
자긴 정말 끝내주는 마누라야!
You are an amazing wife.
정말이야, 정말 날 위해
이걸 준비했던 거야?
Really, you are amazing. You were
actually gonna do this for me?
이런 이해심과 강인함은
대체 어디서 나오는 거야?
Where do you find the strength
and the understanding for that?
실은 나 지금 엄청 취했어
I'm very, very drunk right now.
보통때 같으면 말 걸겠는데
자신감이 좀 없어졌어
Ordinarily, I would talk to her,
but my confidence is shaken.
저 여자랑 과연 잤나, 안잤나
Did I sleep with her?
Did I not sleep with her?
너한테 경종을 울린거야
너의 여자 만나는 태도에 대해서 말야
Maybe this is a wake-up call. You know,
about your whole dating attitude.
서른 넘도록 진지하게 사귄
여자 하나 없잖아
You're in your 30s and you have
never been in a long-term relationship.
이 여자, 저 여자,
Here you go from woman to woman..
의미없는 관계의 연속일뿐
meaningless experience
to meaningless experience.
관계가 깊이 발전하지 않는다고
걱정하는 법도 없고
Never even worrying that it doesn't
turn into something more serious.
맞아!
정말 멋진 인생이야
You're right. I love my life!
나 저 여자랑 잤어!
I actually did sleep with her.